<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting-starteds on Light OAuth2 - OAuth2 Serivces based on light-4j</title>
    <link>https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting-starteds on Light OAuth2 - OAuth2 Serivces based on light-4j</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 10:12:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OAuth2 Introduction</title>
      <link>https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 10:12:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/introduction/</guid>
      <description>OAuth 2 is an authorization framework that enables applications to obtain limited access to user&amp;rsquo;s resources on an HTTP service - normally exposed as a REST API. It works by delegating user authentication to an authorization service which contains all sorts of login service providers like LDAP for employees and database for customers.
OAuth 2 provides authorization flows for the following types of application to application communication:
 Web server to API Standalone application to API API to API  This informational guide is geared towards application developers, and provides an overview of OAuth 2 roles, authorization grant types, use cases, and flows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 21:20:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://networknt.github.io/light-oauth2/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>OAuth2 Introduction If you are new to OAuth2, please read this introduction document to get familiar with the concept.
Select the Right Edition Enterprise Edition A microservices and database based OAuth2 server that have 7 services and numeric endpoints to support user login, access token, user registration, service registration, client registration and public key certificate distribution. It can support millions users and thousands of clients and services with scopes. It should be easily handle thousands of concurrent users per instance and each microservice can be scaled individually.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>